[cell phone rings]
Morning, Lisbon.
Morning. You close?
No. Flat tire.
Alright. We'll talk
when you get here.
Wait, just 'cause I'm not there
doesn't mean I can't help.
Hold on a sec.
What do you got?
Victim's name is
Michelle Karp...
I'm putting you on speaker.
'Nineteen. She left
the restaurant where she worked'
'around 11:00 p.m.
Never made it home.'
She was abducted and murdered.
Her body was dumped
here last night.
Walker found her
an hour ago.
- Thanks.
- Alright.
[sighs]
The body's
on state park land
near a picnic area
not far from the road.
How was she killed?
Her throat was slit.
It looks pretty clean, precise.
- Mm. Blood?
- 'Hardly a drop.'
She's fully clothed,
so probably no sexual assault.
'Her hands and feet
are bound with wire.'
Small pebbles have been
placed on her eyes.
Huh, nice touch.
Pebbles from the crime scene?
It looks like it, yeah.
And the...oh. And the wire?
It's knotted.
Neatly, carefully.
Someone took their time.
Yeah, you're right.
I didn't say anything.
No, but you were thinking
whoever did this
has killed before
many times.
Yes, but I can't
assume that.
Trust your instincts,
Lisbon.
Boss. Just got off the phone
with Fresno P.D. The killer's
'M.O. fits four other murders
they've had in 18 months.'
Looks like we've got
a serial killer.
'Huh? See?'
You called it, Lisbon.
You called it!
[theme music]
Fresno P.D. sent over
their files an hour ago.
Here's what we got so far.
The San Joaquin killer
abducts young girls.
All between the ages
of 16 and 20.
He takes them to a location
where he binds their hands
and feet with wire, cuts
their throat and dumps them.
Objects found near the crime
scene are placed over the eyes.
Pebbles, glass pieces,
and bottle caps so far.
Any pattern to where
the bodies were found?
It seems random, but --
Fresno P.D. said the girls
were taken at opportune moments.
Often the only time
they were alone.
Meaning he stalks them first.
Does Fresno P.D.
have a suspect?
Yep.
- Eight suspects?
- 'Yeah.'
Due to the lack of evidence, the
list hasn't been narrowed down.
Grab Cho, get the list of names,
and talk to them.
- Meh.
- What?
You're just going
through the motions.
Yeah, it's called
police work.
Well, why not try
a fresh approach?
Like what, tarot cards?
Go directly to the one
that feels right.
Look, these are all
viable suspects.
The Fresno P.D. did
their job well.
So you're gonna do
the same job over again?
Take a close look at these guys.
Use your intuition.
Which one is guilty?
- I don't know.
- Oh, come on.
You've been
a cop for a while.
What you don't know is what you
know without knowing.
- Take a guess and run with it.
- Alright. Okay.
- Okay.
Not him.
Bow tie, no.
[photo rustles]
Or him.
It could be him.
Sneaky eyes.
On the other hand,
he's got a college education.
That profiling blather,
forget about that.
Go with your gut.
[sighs]
There. In seconds,
you've whittled it down
to a manageable
three suspects.
Which one of these guys
jumps out at you?
[telephone rings in distance]
This one?
Yeah, but it's just a hunch.
I don't know why.
Best kind of hunch.
As good a place to start as any.
Nicely done, Lisbon.
[Van Pelt]
'His name is Richard Haibach.'
'He's 44 years old,
lives alone.'
He has an alibi for two murders,
but Fresno P.D. logged
complaints against him
for loitering.
Apparently he likes to park
outside local high schools.
'Including one
a victim went to.'
- That's all I got.
- Alright.
You mind waiting here?
I want to talk to him on my own.
Sure.
Richard Haibach?
Who are you?
I'm agent Lisbon
with the CBI.
You mind if I ask you
a few questions?
- Actually, I do.
- It shouldn't take long, sir.
- Can I come in?
- Uh, not without a warrant.
Okay. Uh, can you tell me
where you were last night?
Home alone all night.
Why, was there another murder?
I can't comment on
an ongoing investigation, sir.
That means there was one.
I'm not dumb.
I've said a hundred times
already.
I've got nothing to do
with this.
Sir, I didn't--
You people just
won't let go.
I'm getting tired being
harassed all the time.
Mr. Haibach, I just
have a few questions.
- Then I'll be on my way.
- I know the law.
I don't have to answer your
questions or tell you anything.
[cell phone keypad beeps]
[rings]
- Hey, boss.
- 'Anything? Updates?'
Yeah, I checked out the other
two suspects on the list.
'The first's been
out of state all week.'
'The FAA flight list
confirms it.'
'The second was with his wife,
kids, and in-laws.'
- Anyone else on the list?
- 'Cho's working those.'
Half alibied out straightaway.
He's starting on the other half.
'Hold off. I want you'
to canvas the crime scene.
See if you can put Haibach
anywhere near there last night.
So? Is he our guy?
I didn't get
a good feeling from him.
[keys jangle, ignition clicks]
So we'll start with
an intro, you know.
Background on
the San Joaquin killer
and then I'll go into
questions for you two.
Um, wait. Excuse me, gentlemen,
one moment, please.
Paul, can you hold
the roll, please?
Mr. Jane, how are you?
- Hello, Karen.
- Okay, listen, I understand.
But I have a new show now.
It's a whole new format.
More intimate, none of that
"gotcha" journalism I did.
Oh. What'd they do,
hold your shoes hostage?
[chuckles]
Very funny.
This week, I'm taking
an in-depth look
at the San Joaquin killer.
I'm hoping you'll join me for
the broadcast Thursday night,
offer your insight, experience.
You don't need me. You have
special agent Wainright here.
He's a good, honest man.
Yes, but he doesn't pop
on camera the way you do.
Oh, Karen, you flatter me.
Good to see you. Be well.
[sighs]
Let's go.
[clears throat]
With me today is special agent
Luther Wainright of the CBI.
Welcome,
and James Panzer
an investigative crime
reporter and blogger.
Mr. Panzer,
we'll start with you.
You've been tracking the San
Joaquin killer for how long now?
Well, it's been, uh, nearly
two years now, Karen.
That's when he took
the life of Molly Maier
a young girl who lived down the
street from me back in Fresno.
Uh, that was his first victim
that we know of.
And pursuing him is pretty much
your life now, right?
You created a web site
devoted to his capture?
Yes, that's right. Molly's
family, they're good people
and they deserve justice. All
his victims deserve justice.
I'm simply trying to help
achieve that goal.
And s-special
Lieutenant Wainright..
Special agent Wainright.
Special Agent.
And special agent Wainright
how close are you
to that goal?
To arresting
the San Joaquin killer?
Well, Karen, we are
absolutely making progress.
[footsteps approaching]
Working on a computer?
What's next,
ray guns, teleporters?
Mm.
Hang on. Hey, Cho.
'Haibach wasn't home
last night.'
He was at a bodega near
the crime scene
an hour before Michelle Karp
went missing.
Owner I.D.'d him, said he was
parked in front
for 20 minutes
before he went inside.
How close to
the crime scene?
Hey, how far
from the crime scene are we?
[mouth full]
Six blocks.
What?
- Six blocks.
- 'Alright.'
I'll work on Judge Waters.
The proximity and the fact
that Haibach lied
should be enough to get him
to sign a search warrant.
'Okay.'
[mouth full]
What?
How do you not feel
that on your face?
Feel what?
[Patrick]
James Panzer?
Patrick Jane.
- Hello.
- Thanks for meeting with me.
Oh, anything I can do to help
with the investigation.
So, James,
what's your deal?
You've devoted your life to
the capture of a serial killer.
That's either very saintly
or very weird.
Well, that's an odd notion
coming from you.
And I know about you,
Mr. Jane.
Ah, I thought you might.
Red John did kill
my family.
Uh, what is it
that gives you cause?
What did Molly Maier
mean to you?
I didn't know her.
I never spoke to her.
I saw her at
the bus stop a few times.
But, uh, it was
such a brutal act.
It was so close to home that it
had a visceral impact
on me that I couldn't shake.
I don't know why.
I mean, people search
for reason or meaning
behind events in their lives,
when more often than not
there is none.
Oh, uh, congratulations,
by the way.
Thank you. For what?
You killed Red John.
Oh, that. Yes. Hmm.
What was that like?
Yeah, uh...not as satisfying
as you might think.
Something occurred to me while
I was reading your web site.
Yes?
The people that post comments
on the site..
Have you considered that one
of them might be the killer?
Well, it's a possibility,
albeit a rather obvious one.
You see, the San Joaquin
killer is not
like other serial killers.
He doesn't kill
for the same reasons.
He commits murder solely
for the immediate pleasure
that he takes in the act.
The media,
other people's reactions..
That's irrelevant to him.
- A purist.
- Exactly.
Consider the way
he murders his victims.
He slits their throats
slowly, carefully
so he can watch the life
drain out of their eyes.
Uh, I apologize if I'm making
you uncomfortable.
Oh, no.
It's in my wheelhouse.
This killer has come
to consume me.
[chuckles]
Mr. Panzer,
how would you feel
about helping me
with this investigation?
[chuckles]
Well, there's nothing
I would like more.
Excellent.
Mr. Haibach, CBI. Open up.
I told you, I'm through
answering your questions.
I'm through being harassed.
I have rights,
like anybody else, right?
I don't wanna
have to talk to you!
This is a warrant to search the
premises. Step aside, please.
[lowered voice]
You clear the back.
I'll wait here.
[door creaks]
[opens door]
Abuse of power.
That's what this is.
[click]
[crackling]
[inhales sharply]
Step aside.
[sniffles]
I said, step aside!
[sniffles and sobs]
[clanking]
Lisbon!
[keyboard clicking]
Did you I.D. any of
the women in the photos yet?
Some, but we haven't
been able to match any
to the San Joaquin
killer's victims.
Haibach would have burned them
first. He's not stupid.
Keep on looking.
His lawyer's on his way.
[keyboard clicking]
He won't talk
without his lawyer.
He's been around the block
a few times with Fresno P.D.
- 'Hmm.'
- "Hmm," what?
He's a meticulous,
maladjusted loner
who's into stalking young women,
and he has no alibi.
'Yeah, he certainly
looks the part.'
I like him for this.
I like him a lot.
[door opens]
[beep]
[door closes]
[Panzer]
'Hello?'
Hi. It's Patrick Jane.
What's your take
on Richard Haibach?
Oh, he's, uh,
one of the suspects
that the Fresno P.D.
identified.
Antisocial, underachiever..
He's viable, but he doesn't
have the intelligence I'd be
'looking for in our man.'
Thanks. I don't disagree.
It's said that the truest motive
for a serial killer
often lies with
the first victim.
Molly Maier.
I was wondering
if you could
introduce me to her family.
I'd be happy to.
Give me an hour or so.
Thanks. Then maybe we can go
over your research?
'Yeah, sure.'
You could come by my apartment
after we visit the Maiers.
- 'Thanks.'
- Okay.
[snaps shut]
Molly had just turned 16
when she was killed.
She didn't even have
her driver's license.
She was walking home
from her girlfriend's house.
Never made it home.
We've been following
the investigation.
Jim's been good enough to keep
us up-to-date with the others.
[voice breaking]
All those girls.
I can't believe nobody's been
able to catch this monster.
We will, soon.
I don't know.
Now don't lose hope. Molly
wouldn't want that, would she?
No, she wouldn't.
This killer will be brought
to justice. You have my word.
You think I could take a look
at Molly's bedroom?
No. I don't want...
of course.
Tom, will you
show him upstairs?
Thank you.
[whispers]
It's okay.
Sorry about the mess.
We really should get around
to cleaning it up.
Truth is, neither of us
has the heart for it.
"Crap recital practice."
D-do you mind, uh...
Oh, uh, sure.
Thank you.
She loved to dance.
That was, uh...
her thing.
[click]
Worked really hard at it.
[Louis Armstrong's "What
A Wonderful World" playing]
♪ I see trees of green ♪
♪ Red roses, too ♪
♪ I see them bloom ♪
♪ For me and you ♪
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
Once she decided
she wanted to do something
there was no stopping her.
Single-minded,
determined.
Just like her mother.
♪ And clouds of white ♪
♪ The bright blessed day ♪
Must have heard this song
a hundred times.
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
♪ The colors of the rainbow ♪
♪ So pretty in the sky ♪
♪ Are also on the faces ♪
♪ Of people going by ♪♪
[Lisbon]
'Counselor?'
We found dozens of pictures
of young women
in your client's house.
That's your justification
for holding him for murder?
That he took pictures?
He's a photographer.
Sexually suggestive photographs
taken without consent.
Taken in public
without any complaints.
That's not even a misdemeanor.
That's a hobby.
He lied about his whereabouts
the night of the murder.
- I was out taking photos.
- Shh.
[clears throat]
Not exactly a capital offense.
Meanwhile, my client has
had to endure
continued police harassment
for a crime he didn't commit.
I did not kill those girls!
Richard, do not
say another word.
Agent Lisbon,
either release him now
or I'm bringing a harassment
lawsuit against you and the CBI
first thing tomorrow morning.
Mr. Haibach,
you're free to go.
[thumps table]
Thank you.
[sighs]
[footsteps recede]
My apartment's upstairs.
Pardon the mess.
[door opens]
[door creaks]
Wow.
[door closes]
Newspaper articles,
background on the victims
interviews with
the victims' families...enjoy.
Hard to know
where to start.
Uh, water? Soda? Coffee?
Water would be great.
Can I just dig in?
Oh, be my guest.
Thank you.
[exhales deeply]
[mutters under breath]
Crime scene...
[clatters]
[Louis Armstrong's "What A Wonderful World" playing]
♪ I see trees of green ♪
Hope you don't mind.
Music helps me think.
Oh, not at all.
I'll put the water over here.
♪ For me and you ♪
♪ And I think to myself ♪
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
The more I think about it,
the more I'm starting to believe
that your analysis of
the San Joaquin killer
may be wrong.
How so?
Well, you said he's a purist.
A man who kills simply
for the pleasure of it.
I'm starting to think
he's a deeply damaged man
who kills out of
a need for attention.
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
Neglected as a child,
I'd guess.
What do you think, Jim?
Well, I think
you couldn't be more wrong.
♪ So pretty in the sky ♪
look, I know
the San Joaquin killer
better than anyone,
as you yourself have said.
I've spent over a year
inhabiting his mind.
This man is brilliant.
He's a genius who's run circles
around the police.
He's killed at will
without repercussion.
♪ They're really saying ♪
This is a man to be feared,
not pitied.
[cell phone rings]
Excuse me.
[ringing continues]
Hello?
[Lisbon]
Jane?
S.F.P.D. found another body.
♪ And I think to myself ♪
Okay.
♪ What a wonderful world ♪
It's him, isn't it?
He's killed again.
Name's Jill Reisert, 18.
It's the San Joaquin killer.
Hands, feet bound
with the same wire
tied in the same knot.
Killed elsewhere,
dumped randomly.
Pebbles on the eyes?
No. No eyes.
[exhales deeply]
Only days
after the last murder.
He has a taste
for attention now.
Bigger city, bigger stage,
bigger violence.
He's getting more
and more excited.
What time was she killed?
Based on the rigor, coroner
thinks it was this morning.
Haibach was free by then.
He could've done it.
No. I know who did this.
James Panzer.
Panzer? The reporter
covering the case?
The Fresno P.D.
would've checked him out.
They did. He had an alibi
for two of the murders.
Both faked, somehow. Look into
them if you don't believe me.
Or don't. I don't care.
I know it was him.
- Evidence.
- That's the problem.
We don't have anything
linking him to the crime.
FBI's pushing to
take over this case.
I'm doing everything
I can to hold them off
but I don't have the pull.
We need an arrest.
I'll get him.
I need time.
- Time we don't have.
- I'll get him.
Okay. How long do you need?
I'll have him in custody
by the morning.
Give you till the morning.
Good luck.
Panzer knows everything
about this case.
'We've got no forensic evidence
and no eyewitnesses.'
How do you propose
we catch him?
We take away
what he wants most.
Mr. Jane.
Any news?
Uh, n-not now, Karen.
Please, give us
a morsel, anything.
Okay. We have a suspect.
We'll be making an arrest
sometime tonight.
We'll announce it to the press
tomorrow morning.
- Who is it?
- You'll find out tomorrow.
Come on. Just tell me if it's
one of the previous suspects.
[scoffs]
It is, isn't it?
- You didn't hear it from me.
- You can trust me.
I mean it. You can't
go public with this today.
I'm only telling you
so you're not caught
off guard
tomorrow morning.
Thank you. Wait. Patrick.
The offer's still open
if you wanna come on my show.
Uh, yeah, thank you,
but no, thanks.
Think about it.
That's all.
Sure.
Dan. Dan.
Call the office
and clear the 7:00 open.
I've got a breaking story.
Alright.
What's going on?
Panzer committed these
murders out of hubris.
He wants to create a mythology
around the San Joaquin killer.
That's why he started
the web site.
He doesn't just wanna kill.
- He wants people to be in awe.
- Yes?
So we arrest someone else
for the murders.
Someone pathetic and unworthy.
Thus destroying his mythology
with one fatal blow.
Panzer will go out and kill
again just to prove us wrong.
And we'll be there
waiting for him.
Arrest somebody else?
Oh..
Are you sure, boss?
I got this.
Oh, come on.
You people just don't quit..
Oh!
You're under arrest.
For what?
We'll think of something.
[Haibach groans]
[doorbell chimes]
[Panzer]
Hello?
Mr. Panzer, it's Patrick.
I have some information.
[buzzer buzzing]
we got him.
San Joaquin killer.
Made an arrest.
I heard about it on the news,
but I didn't believe it.
- Who is it?
- Richard Haibach.
- I thought he had an alibi.
- Faked.
Lied about the whole thing,
which isn't difficult to
pull off if you know
what you're doing.
You're certain
that it's him?
We found pictures of
women in his home.
Two of the victims
were amongst them.
That doesn't prove
he's the killer.
We found something else.
I can't comment on specifics.
But the A.G.'s office
is confident that it
along with Haibach's proximity
to the Karp murder
and the photos will be enough
for a conviction.
We'll announce it to the press
tomorrow morning.
I wanted you to know first,
given your...
personal attachment to the case.
And I wanted to stop by
and say thanks for your help.
Oh, yes, of course.
Look, can I get you
a drink or something?
No, thanks. Do you mind
if I use your restroom?
Oh, sure, sure.
Right-right over there.
- End of the hall here?
- Yes.
[toilet flushes]
[cabinet door creaks]
[switch clicks]
You sure you don't want
a drink or a snack?
Oh, no. I have to get going.
[sighs]
[door opens]
You know,
it's funny, isn't it?
What's that?
We were both wrong
about the San Joaquin killer.
He wasn't a purist, nor was he
a man desperate for attention.
He was just a sick,
sexually deranged man
that likes to take pictures
of little girls.
Simple-minded pervert.
Goodnight.
[door closes]
[whispers]
Come on.
[door opens]
[door closes]
There he is.
[alarm chirps]
[engine starts]
Wait.
[alert chiming,
seat belts click]
[Lisbon]
I'll call S.F.P.D. for backup.
[whispering]
Jane!
Um...Lisbon?
Couldn't stay away,
could you?
[desk clangs]
Put your hands in the air.
Step back from the table.
What are you doing here?
I said put your hands
in the air now!
Look, you don't understand.
I j--
What are you doing here?
Turn the camera off.
Karen called me
about an hour ago.
She gave me this address.
She asked me to meet her here.
I've never been
here before in my life.
- I said turn the camera off.
- Turn it off.
- You called him?
- He's the expert.
I wanted him to authenticate
that this was
'the kill room used
by the killer.'
How did you know
about this place?
She was contacted by him,
by the San Joaquin killer.
Yes. Just after
my 7:00 broadcast
'during which I announced
the CBI had someone in custody.'
Someone texted me
from a blocked number
said he was the S.J.K.
and gave me this address.
Alright. Out.
This is officially
a CBI crime scene. Let's go!
[breathes deeply]
I tried to tell you
you had the wrong man.
You set this up.
You knew we were
following you.
I don't know what
you're talking about
but I admit,
I'm very hurt by all this.
I mean, here I thought
you were seeking my help.
That we were kindred spirits.
Where all along
you were just lying to me.
You were using me.
That kind of duplicity..
Leading a double life,
I don't know how you do that.
'Agent Lisbon, Jane.'
I'd like you to meet
FBI special agent Susan Darcy.
As of this morning,
her team will be
taking over the investigation.
- Sir--
- No, it's okay. It's fine.
The man you want
is James Panzer.
What sort of evidence
do you have on Panzer?
- Well, nothing--
- Nothing concrete.
Not, uh, your kind
of evidence, anyhow.
How about your kind
of evidence?
His medicine cabinet
is too neat.
That's an interesting
perspective.
I'll absorb the case files
and if Panzer looks like
a good unsub
you can be rest assured
that we will be on him.
- No, you won't.
- Jane?
While she's absorbing the case
files, Panzer will kill again.
You're not being
constructive right now.
- I'm just being honest.
- It's okay.
I understand you're upset.
You have every reason
to be upset.
I would be, too, if someone
was taking over my case.
If he does kill again,
it will be my responsibility,
And I will answer for it.
But let me be very clear.
This investigation is now under
the jurisdiction of the FBI.
It's all yours.
I need those case files
as soon as possible.
Yeah.
Jane.
Jane, you heard Wainright.
Our hands are tied.
Yeah.
Yeah. Maybe yours are.
[jazz music]
Well, Karen, no disrespect
to the CBI or the FBI
but it's not a good sign
when a case as complex
and important as this one
is shuttled
from agency to agency.
There's, there's a lack of
communication and consistency.
There's a pointless
replication of effort.
You see the same problems in the
search for the zodiac killer.
Uh, hold that thought, James.
We'll be right back
after a quick break
with our guest, James Panzer,
and a surprise special guest
CBI consultant
Patrick Jane.
And clear.
I hope you don't mind.
But--
Patrick.
Thank you so much
for coming, really.
Hi.
We're getting Mr. Jane
mic-ed?
Yes, we are.
[male #1]
In five, four, three, two...
[jazz music]
Joining us now on this S.J.K.
special edition is Patrick Jane
'a consultant with the CBI'
who has his own amazing story
of terrible tragedy
and cold revenge. Patrick,
thank you for joining us.
Oh, it's my pleasure, Karen.
James.
In a nutshell,
why has the San Joaquin killer
proven so difficult
to apprehend?
Well, James is exactly right.
There are too many cooks
in the kitchen.
But I-I would also like to add
that the San Joaquin killer
is very likely someone
that has attached themselves
to the investigation somehow.
Someone, uh, hiding
in plain sight.
That's interesting.
Is there anyone
in particular
that you're thinking of?
We have our suspicions.
Well, that sounds promising.
Can we expect an arrest
anytime soon?
Very likely.
Karen, if I may ask Jane
a question, I'd--
- Could you hold that thought?
- Well, I--
Can-can you elaborate
on that, Patrick?
What makes you think that
the San Joaquin killer
will be caught soon?
Well, he's become wrapped up
in his own mythology.
Uh, he's drank his own
Kool-Aid, so to speak.
Well, there is absolutely
nothing to suggest that.
You're right, James,
I have no evidence.
Just a good sense
of the man.
The San Joaquin killer
is a sad little person
living in a fantasy world
of power and prestige.
It's only a matter of time
before he makes a mistake.
Jim?
I'd like to say I believe
what Mr. Jane is saying
but I can't disagree more.
I mean, this man is smart,
he is rational
he's brilliant, in fact.
Hmm. I-I respect your skills
as a journalist
and as a blogger, James,
but I do this for a living.
I don't think you know
or understand this man at all.
Well, that's absurd!
I mean, that's just...
That's... your opinion,
and I respect that.
But, Patrick, I mean,
I think you should
consider the plain facts.
James, hold that thought.
If I could just
respond here.
You'll have that chance
when we come back with more
on the search for
the San Joaquin killer.
[male #1]
'We're clear.
30 seconds, everyone.'
Great stuff, guys.
I know what you're doing.
You think I'm stupid?
Yes.
You're not going to
ruin this for me.
When we come back,
Jim, you're up.
[male #1]
'Ten seconds.'
'In five, four'
'three, two..'
James Panzer may be
the man who knows
the San Joaquin killer best.
Tell us, Jim,
will he kill again?
Well, Karen,
I hate to say this
but, yes, I-I think this man
will strike again
and I think that there will be
many, many more victims.
A dark prediction.
Uh, what makes you
think that?
Well, he is growing more bold
and more confident every day.
More sure of his abilities
and his greatness.
'And why shouldn't he be?'
'He's been able to evade
detection so easily.'
He is too good to be caught.
Patrick, thoughts?
Patrick?
It's funny. Red John thought
exactly the same thing.
[scoffs]
Somehow, I don't think
the San Joaquin killer
will be quite as easy
to kill as Red John.
You're very much mistaken.
Red John was an accomplished
killer, no doubt.
And I applaud you
for ridding us of him.
But there is no comparison
to the San Joaquin killer.
'Red John was
a common sociopath.'
Lazy, sloppy, delusional.
You really have no idea
what you're saying.
- Red John--
- Red John is dead.
And the fact
that he allowed himself
to be caught and killed by you
just proves my point.
Compared to S.J.K.,
Red John was nothing.
An amateur, already forgotten.
[knock on door]
You, uh..
...you were very good
out there.
Well...thank you.
I wasgood.
[cell phone vibrating]
Hello?
Where?
[dramatic music]
[police radio chatter]
What's happened?
Panzer. See for yourself.
[theme music]